addatimes.com 2017-03-26

# Addatimes.com

We value the trust placed in use by You and therefore, we follow the highest standards of privacy guidelines to protect the information shared by You with us.

This Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) governs the use of Personal Information shared (as de䏖ned below) with or collected by ADDATIMES MEDIA PRIVATE LIMITED from the users ofAddatimes. This Privacy Policy is subject to change from time to time without any written notice to You. Please review the Privacy Policy from time to time to be updated with the latest changes and modifications.

By browsing, using, downloading or installing Addatimes, You agree to be bound by the terms of this Privacy Policy. If You do not agree with the terms contained herein, please do not download or browse Addatimes.

By mere browsing or use ofAddatimes, You consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy and agree to the use of Your Personal Information in the manner as provided under this Privacy Policy.

All capitalized terms that have not been speci䏖callyde䏖ned herein shall have the same meaning as provided under the Terms of Use.

This Privacy Policy should be read in conjunction and together with the Terms of Use available on www.Addatimes.com/terms (http://www.Addatimes.com/terms)

Collection and Use of Personal Information

‘Personal Information’, ‘Information’ and ‘Sensitive Personal Data or Information’ shall have the meaning ascribed to it under the IT Act, 2000 and Information Technology (Reasonable Security Practices and Procedures and Sensitive Personal Data or Information) Rules, 2011. Generic Information/Financial Information  
Demographic Information

Cookie

We collect Your Personal Information or Information when You use or browse Addatimes and at the time of Your registration with Addatimes and You share such information with Us through email or by posting on Addatimes or by any other means made available to You by Us. We collect information with respect to Your name, mobile number, email, address, IP Address, zip code, age, gender, occupation etc. Based on Your purchase of subscription package, our payment gateway partners collect information with respect to Your credit/debit card details or other bank account details. This information is stored by our payment gateway partners.

We collect information in order to provide You with a safe, effcient, smooth and customized experience. This allows Us to provide services and features that most likely meet Your needs, and to customize Our Addatimes to make Your experience safer and easier.

Except as provided herein, We do not solicit any Sensitive Information about You. However, if You share such information with Us voluntarily, We will not be liable for any actions, claims, costs, expenses or other liabilities that may arise as a consequence of such any unauthorized use or misuse of such information.

We may track certain information about You based upon Your behavior on Addatimes. We use this information for conducting internal research on Our users' demographics, interests, and behaviour to better understand, protect and serve Our users. This information is compiled and analyzed on an aggregated basis. This information may include the website that You just visited (whether this website is on Addatimes or not), which website You next visit, Your computer browser information.

We may also collect Your Information to track user behaviour and preferences for internal analytics and research. We may also use Your information: (i) to evaluate Your interest for various genres of content, services, offers; (ii) to perform analytics and conduct customer research, to determine Your interest, for identifying Content that generate sales and to analyses traffic patterns.

If You choose to post messages on Our message boards, chat rooms or other message areas or leave feedback, We will collect that information You provide to Us. We retain this information as necessary to resolve disputes, provide customer support and troubleshoot problems as permitted by law.

If You send Us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other users or third parties send Us correspondence about Your activities or postings on Addatimes, We may collect and store such information.  
We identify and use Your IP address to help diagnose problems with Our server, and to administer Addatimes. Your IP address is also used to help identify You and to gather broad demographic information.

We will occasionally ask You to complete optional online surveys. These surveys may ask You for contact information and demographic information (like zip code, age, or income level). We use this data to tailor Your experience at Addatimes, providing You with content that We think You might be interested in and to display content according to Your preferences.

A "cookie" is a small piece of information stored by a web server on a web browser so it can be later read back from that browser. Cookies are useful for enabling the browser to remember information speci䏖c to a given user. We place both permanent and temporary cookies in Your computer's hard drive. The cookies do not contain any of Your personally identi䏖able information.

You will always have an option not to provide certain information and can choose to opt-out from provision of certain information.

Disclosure of Personal Information with Third Parties

We may disclose Personal Information to af䏖liates and group companies. We may also disclose Your Personal Information with third parties strictly on con䏖dential terms. We may disclose such information to third parties in order to provide You access to Addatimes and facilitate or Your participation in any contest, game or activity conducted by ADDATIMES MEDIA PRIVATE LIMITED, to comply with Our legal obligations, to enforce Our Terms of Use, to facilitate Our marketing and advertising activities, or to prevent, detect, mitigate, and investigate fraudulent or illegal activities related to Addatimes.

We will always take Your express consent at the time of sharing Your Personal Information with third parties for their marketing and advertising purposes.

In the event of any requirement by court order, government or quasi-government agency to disclose Your Personal Information, We will disclose information as may be legally required. We may also disclose Your Personal Information if We, in the good faith believe that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process.

In the event ADDATIMES MEDIA PRIVATE LIMITED is merged with or acquired by another company or in case of re-organization or re-structuring of business, We and Our affiliates will share Your Personal Information, wholly or in part, with another business entity.

Third Party Sites

Addatimes may provide links to various third party websites that may collect Your Personal Information. Use of Your information collected by such third-party website will be governed by the privacy policy in such third-party website. ADDATIMES MEDIA PRIVATE LIMITED has no control on the operation of such third-party websites and You may share information with such third party at Your sole risk. ADDATIMES MEDIA PRIVATE LIMITED shall not be liable to You for any misappropriation of Your Personal Information by such third party.

Promotional and Marketing Activities

We will send communications to You at regular intervals to notify You of, among other things, various offers, new content, exclusive deals etc., that may be available or new services that You may be interested in subscribing etc. By accessing Addatimes, You expressly consent to receive such communications from us at regular intervals.  
However, if You do not wish to receive any communication from us, You may request to opt-out by sending an email to support@addatimesmedia.com (mailto:support@addatimesmedia.com---subject=Unsubscribe) with the subject as “Unsubscribe”.

Security and Compliance with Laws

We strive to protect Your Personal Information against unauthorized disclosure, misuse, unlawful use, modification, loss or destruction. We take all reasonable measures and precautions, as per standard industry practices, to keep Your Personal Information confidential. We ensure compliance with all applicable laws including but not limited to Information Technology (Reasonable security practices and procedures and sensitive personal data or information) Rules, 2011.

Amendments

We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to modify the terms of this Privacy Policy from time to time in order to ensure compliance with applicable laws (“Updated Terms”). The Updated Terms shall be effective immediately and shall supersede these the terms of this Privacy Policy. We will not be under an obligation to notify you of any changes to this Privacy Policy. You shall be solely responsible for reviewing the Privacy Policy from time to time for any modifications. By continuing to use Addatimes after the Updated Terms have been published, You af䏖rm Your agreement to the Updated Terms.

Contact Us

If You require any information or clarification regarding the use of Your Personal Information or this Privacy Policy, You can contact us at support@addatimesmedia.com (mailto:support@addatimesmedia.com)  
If You have grievance with respect to use of Your Personal Information, please email to support@addatimesmedia.com (mailto:support@addatimesmedia.com)

ADDATIMES MEDIA PRIVATE LIMITED is a company based in India. By browsing/using Addatimes, You hereby acknowledge that ADDATIMES MEDIA PRIVATE LIMITED is not responsible or liable in any manner to comply with any local laws of Your territory except India with respect to Addatimes.

is being covered by these top rated media channels
